Finding Aid for the Alfred Leonard and Joseph Leonard Collection PASC-M.0180
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Correspondence, Series III.
  - P. Alfred Leonard and Ernst/Lilly Toch, Subseries 1.
    - Toch, Lilly. [Letters to Alfred Leonard and Elizabeth Winston]. 2 leaves; envelope. (Box 4, Folder 26)
      Contains 3 items: letter dated January 8, 1962 from [Lilly Toch?] to Elizabeth Winston regarding catalogue of Toch's works and proposed ASCAP dinner; cover letter from Lilly Toch to Alfred Leonard regarding letters sent from Columbia recording project and asking for feedback on communication with Steinberg; envelope dated January 9, 1962.
    - Toch, Lilly. [Letter to Alfred Leonard]. 7 leaves. (Box 4, Folder 27)
      Contains 6 items: cover letter dated October 19, 1962 from Lilly Toch to Alfred Leonard regarding Franzi's perception of Toch's being slighted in Life Magazine article; 3 page biography of Ernst Toch; clipping from Dutch newspaper on Los Angeles festival performance of Toch's works; 2 typewritten letters to Life Magazine noting omission of Toch's name in article; envelope.
    - Leonard, Alfred. [Letter to Lilly Toch]. 2 leaves. (Box 4, Folder 28)
      Letter dated October 29, 1962 regarding Leonard's response to omission of Toch's names in Life magazine article and proposal for response from other artists.
    - Director of the Austrian Institute. [Invitation to attend reception for Ernst Toch's 75th Birthday celebration]. card. (Box 4, Folder 29)
      Dated December 18, 1962.
    - Toch, Lilly. [Note and xeroxes to Alfred Leonard]. note; xeroxes; envelope. (Box 4, Folder 30)
      Contains 3 items: note in Lilly Toch's handwriting; 3 pages of xeroxes with extracts from newpaper reviews of Big Ben dating from 1934; 1935, and 1963; envelope marked "Big Ben Op. 62".
    - Toch, Lilly. [Note on back of envelope to Alfred Leonard]. airmail envelope. (Box 4, Folder 31)
      Note in back of envelope in German dated February 29, 1964.
    - Toch, Lilly. [Letter to Alfred Leonard]. 1 leaf; 15 pp; 1 envelope. (Box 4, Folder 32)
      Contains 7 items: cover letter dated April 26, 1966 from Lilly Toch to Alfred Leonard regarding the price of the Schott publication; xerox of article by Nikolai Lopatnikoff on Ernst Toch; article by Toch entitled "Some Thoughts Out of Season"; pamphlet on Schott edition of Toch's Concerto for cello and orchestra; pamphlet on Schott edition of Toch's Piano Concerto Opus 38; xerox of review of Toch's works in German; airmail envelope.
    - Toch, Lilly. [Letter to Alfred Leonard]. 1 leaf. (Box 4, Folder 33)
      Letter dated May 2, 1968 regarding Heifetz-Piatigrosky performance of Toch's works.
    - Antonini, Alfredo. [Letter to Lilly Toch]. xerox; 1 p. (Box 4, Folder 34)
      Letter dated September 18, 1968 regarding Antonini's performance of Toch's Symphony for Piano and Orchestra Op. 61.
    - Toch, Lilly; Pietsch, Karl Peter. [Letter to Marjorie and Alfred Leonard]. 1 leaf; xerox 5 pp; envelope. (Box 4, Folder 35)
      Contains 5 items: cover letter dated April 6, 1970; xerox of letter in German dated October 21, 1969 from Karl Peter Pietsch of Bayerischer Rundfunk to Lilly Toch; 3-paged xerox of Ernst Toch poem in German; 1-paged xerox of Ernst Toch poem in German; envelope.
    - Toch, Lilly. [Letter to Alfred Leonard]. 1 leaf. (Box 4, Folder 36)
      Letter dated September 9, 1969 expressing regret for using Leonard's private address.
    - Vaughn, Denis. [Letter to Alfred Leonard]. xerox; 1 p. (Box 4, Folder 37)
      Letter dated December 3, 1969 regarding receipt of Toch scores, ideas for staging and which works to pair with Toch works in performance.
    - Toch, Lilly. [Letter to Alfred Leonard]. 1 leaf; xerox 1 p; 2 envelopes. (Box 4, Folder 38)
      Contains 4 items: cover letter in German dated January 12, 1970; xerox of article by Pierre Hugli on Toch; 2 airmail envelopes.
    - Jezic, Diane. [Letter to Lily Toch]. 1 leaf. (Box 4, Folder 39)
      Letter dated July 10, 1970 expressing Jezic's interest in doing doctoral research on Toch and request for information regarding letters and essays in UCLA archives holdings.
    - Jezic, Diane. [Letter to Lilly Toch]. 1 leaf. (Box 4, Folder 40)
      Letter dated July 24, 1970 acknowledging Lilly's response of July 15th.
    - Toch, Lilly. [Letter to Alfred Leonard]. 1 leaf. (Box 4, Folder 41)
      Letter dated July 30, 1970 reporting on family members; on Pittsburg Symphony's Steinberg's performance of Toch's works in November and following season.
    - Leonard, Alfred. [Letter to Gil]. 1 leaf. (Box 4, Folder 42)
      Letter dated March 10, 1977 enclosing notes from speech given by Leonard on Toch 12/7/1962; speech not enclosed here.
    - Toch, Lilly; Toch, Ernst. [Undated letters to Alfred Leonard]. 6 leaves; 1 card. (Box 4, Folder 43)
      Contains 6 items: letter from Lilly mentioning St. Louis synagogue performance of Cantata of the Bitter Herbs; English version by Herman Zipper of unidentified source; report on family members and health [possibly dated 1970 due to reference of Steinberg's resignation]; torn letter in German from Zurichwith references to Opera and Boston performance; letter from Ernst Toch mentioning ongoing work on Second Symphony, warm reception of Toch's works in Scandanavian countries, reprint of 1st Symphony by Schott-Mainz and Klemperer performance, title of "Dedication", writing of Second Symphony while confined to bed rest; handwritten letter from Lilly in German mentioning Thomas Mann; 2-paged torn typewritten letter in German from Lilly and Ernst from Zurich mentioning upcoming performances of Toch's works in Europe; card from Ernst responding to telegram on Ernst's brithday.
    - Winston, Elizabeth. [Letter and contract to Robert Braunschweig]. 2 leaves. (Box 4, Folder 44)
      2 items: cover letter dated July 24, 1971 enclosing contract for public relations work with Ernst Toch and Alfred Leonard, with estimate of expenses; unisigned contract dated July 24, 1971 to Braunschweig.
    - Fry, Stephen. [Letter regarding UCLA Toch archive]. 2 leaves. (Box 4, Folder 45)
      Form letter dated April 12, 1977 regarding progress of UCLA Toch archive, soliciting donations.
  - P. Alfred Leonard and Babin-Vronsky, Subseries 2.
    - K., Alan; Leonard, Alfred. [Letter, memo and draft of essay on Babin-Vronsky piano duo]. memo 1 p; 1 leaf letter; typewritten ms 5 pp. (Box 5, Folder 1)
      Contains 3 items: memo dated 7/5/60 from A. K. to Alfred Leonard "see attached"; note dated 7/5/60 from Alan to Alfred asking Alfred to edit text on Babin-Vronsky; 5 page text by Leonard on Babin-Vronsky piano duo to be used for liner notes.
    - Babin, Victor. [Letter to Alfred Leonard]. 1 leaf. (Box 5, Folder 2)
      Cover letter dated September 2, 1961 enclosing material on Babin-Vronsky, strategy for cover of RCA recording. Enclosed material missing here.
    - Babin, Victor. [Letter to Alfred Leonard]. 1 leaf. (Box 5, Folder 3)
      Cover letter dated October 18, 1961 enclosing reply to RCA. Reply missing here.
    - [Leonard, Alfred?]. [Letter and clipping to Babin-Vronsky]. 1 leaf; newspaper clipping. (Box 5, Folder 4)
      Letter addressed c/o Columbia Artistic Management with note "Mazeltov!", enclosing newpaper clipping review of Babin-Vronsky concert at Carnegie Hall dated February 14, 1962.
    - Babin, Victor; Vronsky, Vitya. [Letter to Marjorie and Alfred Leonard]. 1 leaf. (Box 5, Folder 5)
      Letter dated December 29, 1963 with New Year's greatings to Leonard family.
    - Babin, Victor; Vronsky, Vitya. [Letter to Leonard family]. 1 leaf. (Box 5, Folder 6)
      Letter dated January 28, 1964 concerning successsful importing of unidentified item.
    - Babin, Victor. [Letter to Alfred Leonard]. card. (Box 5, Folder 7)
      Letter dated August 3, 1970 concerning successful proposal for Babin-Vronsky recording with RCA.
    - Babin, Victor; Vronsky, Vitya. [Letter to Alfred Leonard]. postcard. (Box 5, Folder 8)
      Card dated October 7, 1970 mentioning Schnabel recording.
    - Babin, Victor; Vronsky, Vitya. [Letter to Leonard family]. 1 leaf. (Box 5, Folder 9)
      Letter with no date mentioning that Babin-Vronsky will be in New York City December 29th and Viktor's tour with the Festival Quartet.
    - Babin, Victor; Vronsky, Vitya. [Letter to the Leonards]. card. (Box 5, Folder 10)
      Card with no date thanking Leonard's for gift of Rachmaninoff.
    - Babin, Viktor; Vronsky, Vitya. [Letter to Alfred Leonard]. 1 leaf. (Box 5, Folder 61)
      Letter dated May 26, 1970 with thanks for evening spent together, reciept of RCA royalty payment, request for "Dance for Two Pianos" recording at reduced cost.
  - P. Alfred Leonard and Artur Schnabel, Subseries 3.
    - Schnabel, Artur. [Telegram to Alfred Leonard]. telegram. (Box 5, Folder 11)
      Telegram dated January 5, 1945 discussing possible March dates for concert, repertoire and fee.
    - Schnabel, Artur. [Telegram to Alfred Leonard]. telegram. (Box 5, Folder 12)
      Telegram dated February 10, 1945 accepting March 14 recital date.
    - Leonard, Alfred. [Letter to Artur Schnabel]. 1 leaf. (Box 5, Folder 13)
      Typewritten letter dated March 14, 1945 expressing appreciation of Schnabel's evening performance as an auspicious beginning.
    - Leonard, Alfred. [Letter to Artur Schnabel]. 2 leaves. (Box 5, Folder 14)
      Letter dated April 11, 1945 expressing thanks for concert, mentioning the foundation of the Music Guild, and requesting a copy of a manifesto from Schnabel to be published in an advanced program for the Music Guild.
    - Leonard, Alfred. [Letter to Artur Schnabel]. 1 leaf. (Box 5, Folder 15)
      Letter dated April 27, 1945 requesting response to April 11th letter regarding next season's concert.
    - Schnabel, Artur. [Letter to Alfred Leonard]. 1 leaf. (Box 5, Folder 16)
      Letter dated May 17, 1945 asking whether previous letter has been received and mentioning no response from Los Angeles Philharmonic regarding joint project.
    - Leonard, Alfred. [Letter to Artur Schnabel]. 1 leaf. (Box 5, Folder 17)
      Letter dated May 22, 1945 soliciting dates for piano solo concert, proposal for additional piano chamber concerts, statement on restricted finances for fees, request for information on newly re-formed Pro Arte Quartet.
    - Schnabel, Artur. [Letter to Alfred Leonard]. 2 leaves. (Box 5, Folder 18)
      Letter dated June 6, 1945 concering possible dates for Los Angeles solo and chamber concerts, fees and possible repertoire.
    - Leonard, Alfred. [Letter to Artur Schnabel]. 3 leaves. (Box 5, Folder 19)
      2 items: 2-paged letter dated June 12, 1945 regarding proposed program for the Music Guild and subscription plan and discussion of Schnabel's proposed fee; version of page 2 outlining list of points needing response from Schnabel.
    - Schnabel, Artur. [Letter to Alfred Leonard]. 2 leaves. (Box 5, Folder 20)
      Letter dated June 19, 1945 regarding schedule for California performances and further discussion of fees.
    - Leonard, Alfred. [Letter to Artur Schnabel]. 1 leaf. (Box 5, Folder 21)
      Letter dated June 26, 1945 accepting proposed $2500 fee, requesting further information on fee for joint performance with Pro Arte Quartet, suggestions for repertoire.
    - Schnabel, Artur. [Letter to Alfred Leonard]. 1 leaf. (Box 5, Folder 22)
      Letter dated June 30, 1945 requesting Music Guild's reconsideration of holding separate series of concerts, further discussion of repertoire to be performed.
    - Leonard, Alfred. [Letter and draft of telegram to Artur Schnabel]. 2 leaves. (Box 5, Folder 23)
      Contains 2 items: letter dated July 17, 1945 asking if Schnabel had received telegram regarding Pro Arte's unavailability and substitution of London Quartet; draft of message for telegram about Quartet substitution.
    - Schnabel, Artur. [Telegram and draft to Alfred Leonard]. telegram; card. (Box 5, Folder 24)
      Contains 2 items: telegram dated July 17, 1945 agreeing to London Quartet; draft of telegram message.
    - Leonard, Alfred. [Letter to Artur Schnabel]. 1 leaf. (Box 5, Folder 25)
      Letter dated August 16, 1945 proposing Schnabel's participation in Music Guild's series of lectures and discussions.
    - Leonard, Alfred. [Letter to Artur Schnabel]. 1 leaf. (Box 5, Folder 26)
      Letter dated December 6, 1945 requesting photographs for promotion of concerts.
    - Schnabel, Artur. [Letter to Alfred Leonard]. 1 leaf. (Box 5, Folder 27)
      Letter dated December 10, 1945 regarding photographs and repertoire for recital program.
    - Schnabel, Artur. [Letter to Alfred Leonard]. 1 leaf. (Box 5, Folder 28)
      Letter dated December 14, 1945 with travel itinerary.
    - Leonard, Alfred. [Letter to Artur Schnabel]. 1 leaf. (Box 5, Folder 29)
      Letter dated December 18, 1945 regarding photo shoot, travel plans, program, rehearsal and season's greetings.
    - Schnabel, Artur. [Letter to Alfred Leonard]. 1 leaf. (Box 5, Folder 30)
      Letter dated December 22, 1945 regarding possible rehearsal times, not performing the Mozart Sonata Fantasy.
    - Leonard, Alfred. [Letter to Artur Schnabel]. 1 leaf. (Box 5, Folder 31)
      Letter dated January 2, 1946 expressing regret at being unable to meet Schnabel's train.
    - Leonard, Alfred. [Letter to Artur Schnabel]. 1 leaf. (Box 5, Folder 32)
      Letter dated January 16, 1946 regarding rental of rehearsal piano.
    - Schnabel, Artur. [Letter to Alfred Leonard]. 1 leaf. (Box 5, Folder 33)
      Letter dated January 17, 1946 approving rental piano.
    - Leonard, Alfred. [Letter to Artur Schnabel]. 1 leaf. (Box 5, Folder 34)
      Letter dated February 11, 1946 regarding performance dates for following year, enclosing check for payment.
    - Leonard, Alfred. [Letter to Artur Schnabel]. 1 leaf. (Box 5, Folder 35)
      Letter dated March 23, 1946 regarding need for dates for next year's proposed performance, expressing regret for not being able to attend New York concert.
    - Leonard, Alfred. [Letter to Artur Schnabel]. 1 leaf. (Box 5, Folder 36)
      Letter dated April 11, 1946 expressing regret that Schnabel will be unable to perform in Los Angeles the following year.
    - Leonard, Alfred. [Letter to Artur Schnabel]. 1 leaf. (Box 5, Folder 37)
      Letter dated December 16, 1946 proposing concert series in Los Angeles 1947-1948.
    - Schnabel, Artur. [Letter to Alfred Leonard]. 1 leaf. (Box 5, Folder 38)
      Letter dated January 8, 1947 suggesting March as possible concert date.
    - Leonard, Alfred. [Letter to Artur Schnabel]. 1 leaf. (Box 5, Folder 39)
      Letter dated January 15, 1947 proposing a series of concerts with Joseph Szigeti.
    - Schnabel, Artur. [Letter to Alfred Leonard]. 1 leaf. (Box 5, Folder 40)
      Letter dated January 28, 1947 relating state of fixed concert dates, desire to give fewer concerts, abandon teaching, and wish to perform with Szigeti.
    - Schnabel, Artur. [Letter to Alfred Leonard]. 1 leaf. (Box 5, Folder 41)
      Letter dated March 2, 1947 relating postponement of decision for concert dates due to waiting for other dates to be confirmed.
    - Leonard, Alfred. [Letter to Artur Schnabel]. 2 leaves. (Box 5, Folder 42)
      Letter dated February 7, 1947 expressing wish for joint recital with Szigeti, chamber concert and solo recital; suggestions for performance dates, and request for information on fees.
    - Leonard, Alfred. [Letter to Artur Schnabel]. 1 leaf. (Box 5, Folder 43)
      Letter dated February 25, 1947 relating information on Szigeti's performance schedule and requesting information from Schnabel.
    - Leonard, Alfred. [Letter to Artur Schnabel]. 1 leaf. (Box 5, Folder 44)
      Letter dated March 26, 1947 requesting information on possible March concert dates.
    - Schnabel, Artur. [Letter to Alfred Leonard]. 1 leaf. (Box 5, Folder 45)
      Letter dated March 29, 1947 providing dates for performance schedule for following season, fee for Szigeti to be the same as for solo recital.
    - Leonard, Alfred. [Letter to Artur Schnabel]. 2 leaves. (Box 5, Folder 46)
      Letter dated April 2, 1947 regarding alternative dates for 1948 concerts, discussion about fees and financial constraints.
    - Schnabel, Artur. [Letter to Alfred Leonard]. 1 leaf. (Box 5, Folder 47)
      Letter dated April 4, 1947 approving March 17th date for performance, suggesting charging higher ticket prices.
    - Leonard, Alfred. [Letter to Artur Schnabel]. 2 leaves. (Box 5, Folder 48)
      Letter dated April 7, 1947 requesting answers to previously posted questions regarding performance with a trio and the question of fees.
    - Schnabel, Artur. [Letter to Alfred Leonard]. 1 leaf. (Box 5, Folder 49)
      Letter dated April 10, 1947 approving proposed fee, suggesting possible repertoire, and rejecting idea of trio.
    - Leonard, Alfred. [Letter to Artur Schnabel]. 1 leaf. (Box 5, Folder 50)
      Letter dated April 14, 1947 regarding location of concert, approval of proposed repertoire.
    - Leonard, Alfred. [Letter to Artur Schnabel]. 1 leaf. (Box 5, Folder 51)
      Letter dated April 18, 1947 proposing re-issue of Schnabel's books.
    - Schnabel, Artur. [Letter to Alfred Leonard]. 1 leaf. (Box 5, Folder 52)
      Letter dated April 24, 1947 responding to Leonard's proposal for reissuse of Schnabel's books, copyright and licensing from Simon and Schuster and Princeton University Press.
    - Leonard, Alfred. [Letter to Artur Schnabel]. 1 leaf. (Box 5, Folder 53)
      Letter dated May 14, 1947 regarding progress of book publication, requesting information on Schnabel's royalties, and confirmation of March 10th date for performance with Szigeti.
    - Schnabel, Artur. [Letter to Alfred Leonard]. 1 leaf. (Box 5, Folder 54)
      Letter dated December 14, 1947 with proposed program for March concert and conveying season's greetings.
    - Leonard, Alfred. [Letter to Artur Schnabel]. 2 leaves. (Box 5, Folder 55)
      Letter dated December 19, 1947 approving Schnabel's proposed program, suggestions for additional pieces, mention of new store opening January 5, conveying season's greetings.
    - Leonard, Alfred. [Note to Artur Schnabel]. 1 leaf. (Box 5, Folder 56)
      Note (possibly from 1945) conveying that Pro Arte Quartet will be in Los Angeles and available to play concert with Schnabel.
  - P. Alfred Leonard and Joseph Szigeti, Subseries 4.
    - Szigeti, Joseph; Talbot, Ethel M. [Letter to Alfred Leonard]. 1 leaf. (Box 5, Folder 57)
      Letter dated May 20, 1964 requesting copy of photos of Szigeti and Schnabel.
    - Leonard, Alfred. [Letter to Joseph Szigeti]. 2 leaves. (Box 5, Folder 58)
      Letter dated June 4, 1964 expressing regret about photos, suggesting possible inquiries, report on family.
    - Szigeti, Joseph. [Letter to Alfred Leonard]. 1 leaf. (Box 5, Folder 59)
      Letter dated June 12, 1964 expressing memory of photos taken at Leonard's home, request that Leonard contact Front for copies, being busy with proof reading, short note from Wanda.
    - Szigeti, Joseph. [Letter to Alfred Leonard]. 1 leaf`. (Box 5, Folder 60)
      Letter dated July 11, 1964 requesting Leonard's correct address, relating lecture tour in Italy on Bach and Beethoven recordings, plan to perform in Bayreuth in mid-August.
    - Talbot, Elizabeth. [Letter to Alfred Leonard]. 1 leaf. (Box 5, Folder 62)
      Letter dated July 16, 1964 forwarding letter [not enclosed] from Szigeti.
  - P. Alfred Leonard and Peter Heyworth, Subseries 5.
    - Leonard, Alfred. [Letter to Peter Heyworth]. 1 leaf. (Box 5, Folder 63)
      Letter dated November 14, 1977 regarding dates for Klemperer performance at Music Guild events 1945-1947; story about missing orchestral parts; finding materials related to Klemperer.
    - Leonard, Alfred. [Letter to Peter Heyworth]. 4 leaves. (Box 5, Folder 64)
      Cover letter dated October 1, 1978 enclosing clippings, photocopies of programs [not enclosed here]; dates and locations of Klemperer concerts; narration of 3 "crisis" events which occured during Klemperer concerts.
    - Heyworth, Peter. [Letter to Alfred Leonard]. 1 leaf. (Box 5, Folder 65)
      Letter dated October 22, 1978 thanking Leonard for Klemperer material.
    - Leonard, Alfred. [Letter to Peter Heyworth]. 1 leaf. (Box 5, Folder 66)
      Letter dated May 22, 1978 apologizing for delay in sending requested materials; query regarding crediting source for material in book.
    - Heyworth, Peter. [Letter to Alfred Leonard]. 1 leaf. (Box 5, Folder 67)
      Letter dated June 9, 1978 promising acknowledgement in forthcoming Klemperer book.
    - Leonard, Alfred. [Letter to Peter Heyworth]. 1 leaf. (Box 5, Folder 68)
      Letter dated April 30, 1984 congratulating Heyworth on Klemperer book.
    - Heyworth, Peter. [Letter to Alfred Leonard]. 1 leaf. (Box 5, Folder 69)
      Letter dated May 7, 1984 thanking Leonard for letter, accepting invitation to stay with Leonards in California.
    - Heyworth, Peter. [Letter to Alfred Leonard]. 1 leaf. (Box 5, Folder 70)
      Letter dated May 15, 1978 requesting reviews of Klemperer's Music Guild concerts and information on "Mystery of the Missing Orchestral Parts".
    - Heyworth, Peter. [Letter to Alfred Leonard]. 1 leaf. (Box 5, Folder 71)
      Letter dated November 22, 1977 acknowledging receipt of dates of Klemperer concerts, requesting copies of press clipping and recollections of Klemperer.
    - Levi, Hermann. [Letters to Alfred Leonard]. 2 leaves; 1 envelope. (Box 6, Folder 3)
      Letters dated December 10, 1935 [in German] and June 25, 1943 [in English] with news on family members in Germany.
  - P. Alfred Leonard and Others, Subseries 6.
    - Front, Theodore; Leonard, Alfred. [Letters between Theodore Front and Alfred Leonard]. 12 leaves. (Box 6, Folder 1)
      Letters dating from August 15, 1964 and from September 26 - December 27, 1973 regarding death of Kolya Graudan [August 15, 1964] and possible sale of items in Leonard book collection [September 26 - December 27, 1973].
    - Zacharais, Heinz. [Letters to Alfred Leonard]. 31 leaves; 2 envelopes. (Box 6, Folder 2)
      Letters in German dated from September 13, 1933 to Weihnachetn 1936 from Leonard's childhood friend. Envelope contains information on Zacharais presumably from Eleanor Rubin.
    - [Letters in German to Alfred Leonard 1933-1972]. 44 leaves; 3 cards; 2 envelopes. (Box 6, Folder 4)
      Letters dating from October 18,1933 - November 14, 1972 in German; 5 leaves of letters and business card are undated; remainder in chronological order.
    - Batelle, Peg. [Letters to Alfred Leonard]. 2 leaves. (Box 6, Folder 5)
      2 items: undated letter dated expressing congratulations and best wishes to Alfred on marriage to Peg Batalle's daughter, Marjorie; undated short note suggesting that Leonard keep his full name and use "Fred" for short.
    - [Bucknall, Nathalie; Laemmle, Carl]. [Letters from movie studios regarding employment opportunities]. 2 leaves. (Box 6, Folder 6)
      2 items: letter dated March 9, 1934 from Carl Laemmle, President of Universal Pictures Corporation, to Samuel Kline regarding introduction to Alfred Leonard; letter dated June 15, 1934 from Nathalie Bucknall, Director of Research at Metro-Goldwyn Mayer acknowledging receipt of application for technical advisor position.
    - Frichtman, Stephen; Frichtman, Frances; Kelley, Paul A. [Letters to Alfred Leonard; excerpt from minutes of First Unitarian meeting]. 12 leaves. (Box 6, Folder 7)
      10 letters and 1 excerpt dating September 12, 1951 to February 23, 1971. Excerpt concerns resolution of support for Stephen Fritchman's statement to Congressional Committee on Un-American Activities. Stephen Frichtman was minister of the First Unitarian Church in Los Angeles.
    - [Letters to Alfred Leonard]. 16 leaves; 2 cards; 2 postcards; 3 envelopes. (Box 6, Folder 8)